Excuse me!
- Hey! Yo!
- Lay it on me.
Come on.
Come on, move your...
- Thank you.
- Hey, somebody took my...
Stop him!
You need some...
Home.
And let's go live
for some breaking news.
Thank you, Jason. I'm coming to you
with the latest wrinkle in a story
that has sent shockwaves through
the financial world of Gotham.
I'm standing before the home
of Ronald Danzer,
the man who bilked investors
out of a reported half a billion
dollars in a vast Ponzi-scheme.
Danzer is currently out on bail
and awaiting trial.
All of them, the judge, the jury,
the DA,
pay them whatever it takes.
I am not going to prison just
because a few dumb bus drivers
and stupid old ladies
lost their damn pensions.
I gotta sneak out,
villagers are here with pitchforks.
You're my lawyer, fix this.
Balloon.
Balloon?
Air balloon.
- Want a balloon?
- What?
No, no. No, thank you, no.
Ronald Danzer?
Who are you?
Help me.
That's Ronald Danzer!
Roll the camera! Roll the camera!
Help me!
In a bizarre turn of event,
a man appearing to be Ronald Danzer
is rising into the air above Gotham
attached to a weather balloon.
Cart was loaded with bricks
for balance.
So Ronald Danzer cheats half
of Gotham out of their savings,
but before he can stand trial,
an unknown man
clips him to a balloon?
No body?
- We're calling this a murder?
- We call it a public service.
Danzer was a bum
he got what he deserve.
I'm gonna go get a Danish,
that's what I deserve.
Damn it.
Somebody find me O'Brian!
Get me some ice!
Who the hell are you?
- Jim Gordon.
Bullock's new partner. Yeah.
Lieutenant Bill Cranston.
Bullock tells me
you're a real Boy Scout.
Don't think we shouldn't
roughing up the skels.
Well, I do have that rights.
I'm gonna have to remember that.
Maybe I get that tattooed on my ass.
Let me show you something, Gordon.
This was a gift from the Gotham
Chamber of Commerce
for my years of service.
I call him O'Brian.
It also happens to be the best
interrogator on the force.
Nice meeting you, Gordon.
Oh, Luke,
say hello to Sergeant O'Brian.
No, no!
I just met Lieutenant Cranston.
The man, the myth, the legend.
He's a thug.
So no fingerprints
and those carts are too easy
to buy or steal to trace.
How are you coming
on the death threats?
I thought we talked about this.
Ronald Danzer was murdered
- it's our job to catch murderers.
- The guy was a crook.
Who had not been convicted
of any crime.
Tell that to the two guys
who killed themselves
because he lost their life savings.
This guys was living high
for 30 years
while the city kissed his ass
and gave him awards
for being such a philanthropist.
So we just let his killer go free?
The guy walks in here
holds out his hands,
I'll arrest him.
Otherwise, I'm content
justice was served.
Like with the Waynes,
is that what you mean?
Mario Pepper killed the Waynes.
We killed Pepper.
That case is closed.
Detective Gordon?
Davis Lamond from Juvenile Services?
You asked to see Selina Kyle.
Could you sign for custody?
When you're finished
you can bring her
to our new facility on Water Street.
She's scheduled to be transferred
upstate tomorrow.
Yeah, that's gonna be delayed.
She has information
about an investigation.
Would you mind stepping back
a bit please?
Wait a minute. Is that one
of those kids that was snatched?
Another closed case.
What is it about the word closed
you don't understand?
This is something else.
Just read the letters,
track the balloons.
I'll be back in an hour.
Yeah, boss. Get right on it.
Where's my pen?
So why do you care
who really killed the Waynes?
Because I wanna see the person
responsible brought to justice.
Did you read that in a book
or something?
And...
I made a promise to the boy.
So?
The killer came from there.
He took the man's wallet
and the woman's necklace.
Then shot them both.
He left the boy alive.
I was up there.
Everyone knows that much.
Plus, the killer's face was covered.
Not at first.
He pulled up his scarf
when he walked toward them.
I saw him for a second.
- You saw him, here, in the dark?
- I can see in the dark.
You don't believe me.
There's the question of whether
you're lying about what you saw
and there's the question
of whether you were even here.
You're not giving me proof.
I told you I stole some chump's
wallet just before it happened.
That was like two blocks from here.
Didn't he report it?
Yes, a man did report
his wallet stolen by a thief
that matches your description
and, yes, the timing does work out
just before the Waynes'
were murdered.
But that doesn't place you here.
I dumped the wallet.
There.
The sewer. Great.
It isn't that I don't trust you
not to run away,
But, well, I don't.
You find the wallet,
you'll let me go, right?
- That's the deal.
- No.
I find the wallet,
that places you here.
- We still have to find the guy.
- That's bull!
That's the deal.
Great.
Son of a bitch,
she was telling the truth.
Oh, Detective.
You're gonna need these.
Hey. Hey, wait a minute.
Lazlo, honey, take a rest.
Poor thing.
Well, well, well.
Detectives Montoya and Allen.
To what do I owe the honor?
Thought we'd pay our respects.
Maybe ask if you'd seen
your friend Cobblepot around.
Oswald?
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen him.
Isn't that funny?
Almost as funny as two detectives
from Major Crimes
looking for a nobody like Oswald.
Can we stop the dance?
He's dead, isn't he?
He was killed because he told us
about Pepper being framed
for the Wayne murders.
He's dead.
But I didn't kill the little snitch.
Where it is, Jim Gordon
pulled the trigger.
You have proof?
What do I look like, a cop?
I only heard that James Gordon
spread poor Oswald's brains
all over the Gotham river.
Why would Gordon wanna
murder Cobblepot?
Just to keep him quiet
about the frame?
Wrong question, gorgeous.
Jim Gordon pulled the trigger,
but who gave the order?
Who could make a cop commit
cold-blooded murder?
Falcone.
Your deductive powers astonish me.
Honestly, I just got a chill.
You know, there's a rumor
going around
that Falcone gave your latest
boy-toy a nasty beating.
You wouldn't be looking for
little revenge now, would you?
I just want justice
for little Oswald.
Hey, Cobblepot.
Hey, you're supposed to be dead.
I'm afraid you have me confused.
My name is Dimitri from Odessa.
I heard you got whacked for ratting.
Fish is gonna pay serious cash
for your skinny ass.
No, no, no. No, please!
Please! She'll kill me!
Why'd you even come back?
I could not stay away.
Gotham is my home! It is my destiny!
You don't see what's coming! I do!
Gotham needs me! I am its future!
If you're its future,
then Gotham's in big trouble.
Yes. Yes, it is.
Can I have a tuna sandwich please.
Alfred, I don't wanna do this.
Stop, I don't wanna do this. Stop.
En garde.
There you go, son. What, what?
Is that all you got?
I don't wanna do this.
What?
There she blows.
The eye of the tiger feel the wind
in your nostrils, Sir Bruce,
the blood in his face.
Sick, mind your head.
Oh, I do beg your pardon, sir,
I sometimes...
Oh, you little bastard. Blood's up.
That's gotta hurt not a bit.
I said stop!
Stop. Down swords, I surrender.
See.
Nice.
So if I smell blood up, isn't it?
Reading these dusty old files.
What is this anyway?
Police file.
Your mum and dad,
how do you get these?
It wasn't hard.
Why do you wanna look at these?
They're horrible.
That will gonna give you nightmares.
I, I have those anyway
and I'm looking for clues.
Well, so you're a detective now,
are you?
- If I found a clue, I am.
- Have you found a clue?
- Not yet.
That Detective Gordon
has promised you
that he will find the person
that killed your parents.
You really believe he will?
He will try.
Of that I am certain.
Yeah, Detective James Gordon,
one of your counselors
brought me a girl this morning
and I signed for custody.
But... That's what I'm saying
I can't bring her back, she got away.
Yeah, well, I'm not happy
about it either.
On edge, Gordon?
I'm fine. How can I help you?
We're just wondering.
When you shot Cobblepot in the head
and dumped his body in the river,
did Falcone pay you?
Or was that more of a favor
to the Don type thing?
Whatever you heard, it's not true.
Oh, so you mean
you didn't kill Cobblepot
or you didn't do it for Falcone?
We thought we'd give you a chance
to tell us the truth.
- Cop to cop.
- You're not listening.
I didn't kill him.
So where were you
on the night of September 17th?
Are you're really asking me this?
Since when did Major Crimes
become IA?
When cops started doing hits
for the mob.
Yeah?
Come back to me
when you have actual proof.
Until then, don't waste my time.
Hey, Gordon, piece of advice?
Take a shower.
Because you stink like a sewer.
- Any job at all. Even dishwasher.
- We're staffed up.
I only ask a chance to prove myself.
- You ever work in a restaurant?
- Not exactly.
Here, you're on your feet all day.
You don't even have the right shoes.
There you are.
I got the owner of a weather
balloon factory down stairs.
Says he's got something for us.
Montoya and Allen came by.
Accused me of killing Cobblepot.
- Damn.
- Somebody must have talked.
Doesn't matter. The fact they're here
means they've got nothing
and they're gonna get nothing.
End of the day,
no one cares about Cobblepot.
Because he deserved it.
Like Ronald Danzer.
Don't make this
into some bigger thing.
You did what you had to do.
And, yes, he probably did deserve it.
He worked for Fish,
she doesn't employ altar boys.
What about Mario Pepper?
- He deserve what he got?
- Hell, yes.
He was a dirt bag
who tried to shoot you, remember?
And I thought we were done
talking about this.
We're done talking about this
when the person who actually murdered
Thomas and Martha Wayne is in jail,
not the person we killed for it.
For the last time, Gordon,
let it go.
Or what?
I'm gonna be the next person
taken out to the pier
to get a bullet in the head?
The interview's waiting.
Pardon me.
You work at the Italian restaurant
across the way, don't you?
Yeah.
And what size are your shoes?
- Nines.
- What a coincidence.
When I saw that balloon go up on TV,
I knew it was one of mine,
and I said to myself, Jimmy-boy,
you better call the cops right away,
or they'll try and pin this on you.
So it was you who called us.
And here I thought my partner
had gone to the trouble
of tracking you down.
And how exactly was one of your
balloons used to kill Ronald Danzer?
It was stole by my bum
of an ex-employee a month ago.
Carl Smikers.
That's what I get for hiring a kid.
- Did he ever mention Danzer?
- Hell, no.
I'm surprised
he even knew who Danzer was.
We ain't talking about one of those
intellectually superior types here.
You got an address?
Yeah, but you find him,
see you can get back the others.
- The other what?
- The other balloons.
A grand a pop those things are.
He stole four!
Forty-seven dollars?
Frankie, I'm coming back next week,
try to show some initiative,
all right?
Okay.
You're a disgrace to drugs dealers.
- Hotdog.
- Get lost.
- I said get lost.
Lieutenant Cranston...
All right.
Let's see.
Let's see what we got here.
What the hell?
Who are you?
Oh, no.
Right.
So no breakfast then?
And no dinner last night?
What's the new program?
Trying to see how long you can go
without eating anything?
If that's the case, I should save
myself the trouble of making it.
Have you seen this?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
The nutter going around
offing people with balloons?
I can think of easier ways
to kill someone.
Master Bruce, forgive me
for uttering the tired old words,
in times like these,
but in times like these,
you really need
to keep your strength up.
I'm just not hungry.
Morning.
Hey. Thank you.
- I tried not to wake you.
- It's fine. I have a meeting.
You okay?
You hardly slept last night.
- Just work.
- This Balloonman thing?
That's what the paper's calling him.
And it says he killed a cop.
You're not in danger, are you?
You don't have to worry about me.
Well, what is it then?
I can see something's bothering you.
Yesterday...
the first victim, Danzer,
was a con man.
And nobody cared.
Now that a cop's been targeted,
the investigation will get
all the support it needs.
It's not right.
Everyone has to matter
or no one matters.
Otherwise, people lose faith.
That's when you get vigilantes.
But that's isn't your fault.
I mean, if anything,
you're giving people faith.
Am I? How?
Your first case
you caught the Wayne killer!
Do you have any idea
what that meant for the city?
You're a hero.
I've gotta go.
Don't matter if you a cop.
You dirty, the Balloonman
gonna get you.
It's time the people of Gotham
realize
that they have to stand up
for themselves.
Hey, Balloonman ought
to get to my landlord next.
He's a crook.
And his name is Harold...
This is wonderful.
This is like my dream
of how today was going to go.
Besides the black eye
to the department,
now we have a vigilante
who kills bad cops.
Cranston wasn't that bad.
But whatever he was
or wasn't guilty of,
Cranston was a lieutenant
in the GCPD.
You don't get to go around
killing cops.
So where are you on this
and the Danzer murder?
We're looking for a man
named Carl Smikers.
He was an employee at the factory
where the balloons were stolen.
We have got uniforms
staking out his apartment,
but he hasn't been back there
since last night.
- And you like him for this?
- Oh, he's guilty.
Leave me in a room with him
he'll be guilty.
He's definitely connected,
but I'm not sure he's the one.
He have weather balloons.
Cranston and Danzer were killed
with weather balloons!
He's the guy.
Smikers never graduated high school.
He's never held a job
for more than a year.
He's got busts for soliciting.
Possession.
Tell her about the other balloons.
What other balloons?
Smiker's boss mentioned
that four balloons are missing.
There're two still out there.
So two more targets.
We have any sense who they might be?
Danzer and Cranston
were both known figures
and known to be dirty.
The killer didn't need any special
knowledge to target them.
So it's likely the next target
is public
and known to be corrupt.
Basically every elected official
in Gotham should stay indoors.
- Find him. Now.
- We will.
"We will?"
What happened to the killer
doing the city a favor?
You're gonna make me think
you actually care.
Listen, smartass, you wanna kill
a corrupt financiers, be my guest.
You kill a cop,
it's a job safety issue.
-We need a plan.
-Relax.
One thing do know
is how to find someone.
Hey.
Hey. Yo.
What'd he tell you?
Nothing. I was just hungry.
Here's the deal.
You wash dishes, mop the floor,
take out the trash,
otherwise, you're deaf,
dumb, and blind.
- I understand.
- No, you don't.
But you will.
This ain't like other places.
And you'll either get it...
Or I'll be fired?
You could say that.
Oh, you have nothing to worry about.
I know that this is
a great opportunity...
Don Maroni!
Good to see you.
A great opportunity, indeed.
So our suspect had a prior
for soliciting two years ago, right?
So one of my girls thought
he looked familiar.
Remembered he liked big brawny types,
so she pointed me to a pimp,
that guy who specialized in that.
He remembered...
After you rough him up a little.
That used to do deliveries
for this dry cleaner, Mr. Chang.
He remembered on top
of everything else,
our guy was a mah-jong nut,
and into these Chinese bookies
for like five grand.
- And they sent you here.
- By way of some bike messengers,
the guy who runs pickpockets
on the south side
and this pot sticker joint
the guy apparently loves.
Dragon Palace.
- We didn't order any...
- Carl Smikers?
Run!
G.C.P.D! You're under arrest!
Stop, or I'll...
Don't move.
Jim, a little help!
Put it down! Put it down now!
You put the MCU
onto that cop killing Oswald.
Falcone finds out it came from you
I mean, I don't mind
what he did to me, it's...
Lazlo, honey.
You're worried about me, aren't you?
But you must remember,
it wasn't you Falcone wanted to hurt.
It was me.
Understand?
Good.
The boy's lost his spine.
Not everyone's built
for beating like that.
What's that new piece
the Roman's been seeing,
what's her name? Natalia, Nadia?
Yeah.
Tell Butch she's going
to have an accident.
Such a shame.
She was a pretty girl.
And get rid of Lazlo
while you're at it.
He's bringing down the mood.
With pleasure.
- Oh, my God!
- Sorry. I knocked.
But I could hear someone in here...
- How did you get in?
- I still have a key, remember?
And you just let yourself in?
Give it to me.
I could have you arrested.
Or I could arrest you?
Anyway, kind of early to get high,
isn't it?
It's been a stressful day.
- And is that all you're doing?
- I'm afraid so.
Disappointed?
Don't play with me, Barbara.
I was there, remember?
- Through all of it.
- You mean you were part of it.
Fine.
- Answer the question.
- Yes, this is it.
And now that you've broken
into my home
and accused me
of being a drug addict,
- you can leave.
- Not until we talk about Gordon.
- He's killed a man.
- You told me. It's not true.
Not Mario Pepper. Another man.
And he killed him on the orders
of Carmine Falcone.
The biggest crime boss in Gotham.
You're lying.
But, you know,
I guess I should be used to that.
True.
When we were together,
I did lie to you.
A lot.
But you always knew.
You looked in my eyes
and knew when I was lying to you.
Am I lying now?
Is it just because I love him?
Is that why you're so determined
to destroy him?
I've been sober for a year, look,
and I know that doesn't erase
the things that I did.
But I still care about you.
I can't stand you
being with this man.
You deserve better.
Leave.
Now.
Ask him where he was the night
that Oswald Cobblepot disappeared.
That's the name of the man he killed.
I'm telling the truth,
I didn't kill those guys.
I mean, a cop?
Why would I kill a cop?
Maybe because you're a thieving,
and cop-murdering pile of crap?
But mind you, that's just a theory.
You admit stealing the balloons.
Yeah, but I owed these loan sharks
and if I didn't pay them
they were gonna cut off stuff.
So if you didn't kill Danzer
and Cranston, who did?
Who'd you sell the balloons to?
I never saw his face.
We had a drop off point
to exchange the balloons and money.
You know what we got here, Jim,
we got us a criminal mastermind.
Not only has the murder weapon
into the stratosphere,
but so are the bodies.
It's a perfect crime!
The bodies will come back.
What're you talking about?
Do you guys not know
how weather balloons work?
Tell us, genius,
or I can beat it out of you.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay, they rise up,
and it gets colder and colder,
and the balloon gets brittle,
the helium expands.
Then what?
It pops.
I'm starting to really
dislike this case.
Where you think
they find shovels that big?
We only have to worry
about one more balloon.
- Who?
- Cardinal Quinn.
He was meditating in his garden.
Alvarez is on his way to the scene.
Now we're gonna have the church
on our back. Great.
Forget the fact that Quinn
was known as the diddling priest.
Here's what we found
in Cranston's pockets.
What wasn't smashed to bits.
Why's your name on this, Jim?
I know who the Balloonman is.
You see, Falcone's
only the boss of Gotham
because people believe he's the boss.
That's what this Arkham thing
is gonna change.
People are gonna see that
the emperor's got no clothes.
I am wasting my breath.
You're an idiot. Get out of here.
Who the hell are you?
I'm sorry, sir.
Hold on. Put that down.
You are listening, huh? You're new.
- What's your name?
- Paolo, sir.
Italian. You don't look Italian.
On my mother's side.
- It's the side I claim.
- A boy who loves his mother.
Here you go.
I was a lot like you.
Started from nothing.
But I kept my head down,
I worked hard. Now look at me.
- Gotham is the city of opportunity.
- Yes, sir. I believe that too.
You hear what I was saying
back there?
Those names, Falcone, Arkham,
mean anything to you?
Honestly, sir,
I didn't hear anything at all.
Attaboy.
The Balloonman has struck
once again.
Cardinal Quinn, accused
of multiple counts of sexual abuse
is the latest victim
of the vigilante.
See this, this is not good.
You don't go around killing priests.
Least not in public.
Go take care of your mother, Paolo.
His name is Davis Lamond, 48.
He's worked at Juvenile Services
for 15 years. No priors.
He didn't show up for work today
and hasn't been back
to his apartment.
We have uniforms at both.
And you're positive he's the killer?
We found a form on Cranston's body
that I'd given Lamond
yesterday morning.
Also keys that opened
Lamond's apartment.
I'm guessing they had a scuffle,
Cranston went through his pockets,
but Lamond managed
to attach him to the balloon.
What caused Lamond to snap?
Not sure.
Lamond's co-workers described him
as thoughtful,
dedicated, sweet, a few said that.
Oh, great, one of those sweet
cop-killing vigilantes.
And what about his last target?
Same profile as all the rest.
Well-known. Seemingly respectable.
- Actually corrupt.
- This is Gotham.
That doesn't exactly narrow it down.
Meanwhile, I have the mayor,
city council,
half the city's judges
and clergy hiding indoors
screaming at the Commissioner
to find the guy.
And guess who he screams at?
We've got his photo out there.
It's just a matter of time.
- Nothing.
- Really?
Your network of Chinese loan sharks
and hookers came up empty?
Gloat later. Let's think about it.
He had destroyed the balloons,
the helium canister,
the carts he was using.
Maybe a storage facility.
A warehouse.
Or an abandoned building.
That's it?
How'd you come up with that?
It's the same thing I just said.
What made you figure this place?
That girl yesterday, Selina,
she told me
she was in a new juvie building.
Lamond, the counselor,
said the same thing
So I'm thinking, what happened
to the old juvie building?
Turns out the city's getting
ready to demo it.
Look, even if he was here,
he's probably gone.
He's only got one balloon left.
He knows we're closing in.
Oh, that's him right there.
Bullock!
Drop the gun now!
I can't do that, Detective.
I'm not done yet.
- One more time, drop it.
- You should be helping me.
You're wasting your breath.
My partner thinks you're as bad
as the scum you kill.
Me, I can see how you're doing us
a favor.
So don't shoot me, all right?
You believe as I do.
I know you're the one
who caught those child snatchers.
- You risked your life.
- So did I.
- You want to protect the innocent?
- Yes. And we have laws for that.
And what good are laws
when they require men like you
Lieutenant Cranston
to implement them?
And you think Ronald Danzer,
you really think
you would ever seen
the inside of a jail?
Or that priest,
why didn't the law punish him?
You know, I have given my life
to the lost children of Gotham
because I wanted
to make a difference.
You know what difference I made?
None.
Because the people running this city
feed off the weak
and the law protects them.
And when the Mayor
rounded up all those children
to send to that prison upstate...
I decided no more.
I would teach them
there are consequences.
So why don't you ask yourself,
Detective
who are you fighting for?
A mayor in the mob's pocket?
Cops on the take?
Or for the weak and the innocent?
Who are you finally?
Oh, forget it.
- What are you doing?
- How do you like that?
- Grab him!
- How does it feel
you hoisted by your own petard!
No, Jim. Jim, what are you doing?
Jim, let go!
Shoot it! Shoot the balloon!
Jim!
Let go!
- Shoot it!
- Just let go!
Shoot it now!
Carmine, what a lovely surprise.
We're not quite open, but for you...
Hello, Fish.
Just stop by on my way to dinner.
I wanted to make sure
there were no hard feelings.
Never.
That's my girl.
Speaking of your girl,
that better be the reason
why you're ditching me tonight.
What's her name again?
- Nadia?
- Natalia.
And no, she had an accident.
I hope nothing serious.
- A mugging.
- Mugging?
Ever since the Waynes were killed
the city has gone crazy.
I hope the punk who did it
paid with his life.
He will when we find him.
Along with anyone who helped him.
Are you hearing any rumblings
from Maroni's camp?
You don't actually believe that
Maroni had something to do
with it, do you?
Like you say, people are acting crazy
and crazy's bad for business,
especially with everything
on the horizon.
You're talking about Arkham.
I thought you had that locked up.
Keep your eyes open.
Hold on. Hold on.
Give me a second.
There will be more like me,
Detective.
- You know that, don't you?
- Not if we do our job.
We will, I will.
You had your chance. All of you.
Who was your last target?
The crusade of the vigilante
known as the Balloonman
ended tonight when
he was apprehended by police,
He was one man who stood up
to the corruption
eating at the heart of Gotham,
willing to break the law
in order to save it.
Well, I imagine criminals of Gotham
are sleeping well tonight.
He killed people.
- That made him a criminal too.
- That's very true.
Can I get you anything else?
No thank you, Alfred.
Right, well, you know,
do try and eat a bit, would you?
Be a shame to have you floating away.
G.C.P.D. claims a win
but this journalist
is left to wonder,
now that the Balloonman's gone,
who will defend the people of Gotham?
This is Channel 7 at 7.00
reporting live
from the former Gotham Juvenile
Facility Center in downtown.
with your minute to minute updates.
Back to the newsroom, John.
You're okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I fell, that's all. I'm fine.
What's wrong?
I want you to know that
you can tell me anything.
This city's sick.
Sick in a way I hadn't realized.
They were taking him away
plus Balloonman killer
I asked him who his last target was
and you know what he said?
It doesn't matter.
He meant the mayor, judges,
anyone in the position of power.
They're all guilty.
But that's not true.
That's how he feels,
that's how they all feel,
everyone.
That's why the city embraced him
because we let them down.
But if people take the law
into their own hands,
then there is no law.
And we're lost.
There are cops who do it.
The same thing he did.
But you never would.
Do you think I could?
No.
I know you, Jim Gordon.
And I love you.
And I'm gonna get you a drink.
I'll get it.
Jim.
Hello, James.
Old friend.